Horrific Nazi Experiments Gone Awry!
She Demons is a horror, science fiction film directed by Richard E. Cunha.
A couple wash up on an uncharted island where Nazi experiments are going on.
Jerrie Turner, played by Irish McCalla.
Fred Maklin, played by Tod Griffin.
Sammy Ching, played by Victor Sen Yung.
Col. Karl Osler, played by Rudolph Anders.
Igor, played by Gene Roth.
Mona Osler, played by Leni Tana.
She Demons is a 1957 American independent black-and-white
science fiction horror film, produced by Arthur A.
Jacobs and Marc Frederic, directed and co-written by Richard E.
Cunha, that stars Irish McCalla, Tod Griffin, and Victor Sen Yung.
Made in the tongue-in-cheek style of Men's adventure magazines, Nazisploitation, and The Island of Lost Souls, the film was
distributed by Astor Pictures in December, 1957 as a double feature with Cunha's Giant from the Unknown (1957).
The film explores themes of dancing, nazi, shipwreck, mad scientist, murder.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking.